Both sides, step forward.
The rules are simple.
Stay within the marked area.
If someone falls outside,
or admits defeat,
it's over.
No serious injuries.
No lethal moves.
That's all.
Clear?
Don't hit my face.
Don't steal my candy.
The fight begins.
Oh no!
I told you not to touch my candy!
My candy!
My Lord!
Jiaojiao,
just forget it.
He's too weak.
He can't take it anymore.
Yeah, My Lord.
We've fought with Dabao before.
He's really not gentle.
Are you made of iron?
It hurts.
Have you forgotten the pain he caused you?
Dabao should teach him a lesson.
Don't stop.
[Still trying to take advantage at this time.]
[Is this the man you want to entrust with your life?]
[Cheng Qi,]
[I can't afford]
[to lose this competition.]
Cheng Qi, are you out of your mind?
Just give up.
I won't give up!
You won't give up?
Put me down!
Put me... put me down!
Cheng Qi!
- My son-in-law! - Cheng Qi!
My son-in-law!
Cheng Qi!
Jiao!
I won!
My dear!
Cheng Qi!
Wake up!
My dear!
Cheng Qi!
My Lady,
why do you have to drive him away?
He really wants to stay.
Yeah, Jiaojiao.
Cheng Qi is just a scholar.
I know his attitude towards
the competition best.
Let him stay at the Escort Agency.
Jiaojiao,
Dabao was the first to fall.
Cheng Qi won the competition.
You have to keep your promise.
We are not the same kind of people.
Now I'm the head of the Xingyun.
Who would want to fall back
after getting on the branch?
Go to the agency
and be a live-in son-in-law.
Hey,
you've been sleeping all day.
Get up.
If you don't get up,
I'll hit you.
My candy.
Cheng Qi.
Stop pretending.
Wake up!
You're smart,
and good at running away.
I asked for Zhen Dabao
to make you back off.
You never dared to push me before.
Why didn't you give up?
The champion of Xingyun can give up.
The speech
can be a story.
I shouldn't have kept you by my side.
You are so talented.
You deserve a bigger stage
than being a live-in son-in-law.
Why
do you have to stay in the agency?
Because I'm the son-in-law of the Sus.
Jiao.
The last words of the son-in-law.
May we look back on the past with fondness,
and grow old
with love.
You said it.
You almost died.
I'm lucky.
My dear,
you finally remember me.
I know you won't forget me.
You still care about me,
like me,
and mind me.
It seems that you are fine.
Who is your wife?
Don't flatter yourself.
You should leave the Escort Agency.
You can go tonight.
What's wrong with you?
It's nothing.
Just a pain.
Where does it hurt?
My heart hurts.
Jiao,
I really know I was wrong.
From now on,
no matter what,
I will never leave you,
and the Escort Agency.
You gave me the warmth of home,
and the soul of writing.
This is my newly written novel.
It's about you and me.
Where are you going?
To get you some medicine.
The injury was not in vain.
Your Majesty,
my son is incompetent.
I've searched all over the capital,
but there's no outstanding talent.
After reviewing,
I had to present the truth to you.
Only then could I share my thoughts.
Grand Preceptor,
do you have any good strategies?
I suggest we bring back Cheng Qi,
and have him study under Lord Yue.
and have him recommended by Mr. Yue
to the Ministry of Rites.
Mr. Yue.
Yes, sir.
If he becomes your disciple,
he can attend the recitation meeting.
Cheng Qi
is indeed a promising talent.
I am willing to take him as my disciple.
The scholar, eager to save someone,
walked right into a trap.
He thought he could stop the danger by pushing away the escort.
But the result was a double loss.
If so,
Cheng Qi is a man of deep affection.
I appreciate his affection
for the Su family.
If he really regards me as a family member,
why can't we discuss together?
He made me
and my whole family
have such a big misunderstanding.
So,
he was just putting on a show for Zhang Xi Yun.
It's not easy for him.
But I still care.
Those words
hurt me
deeply.
He's right.
He's talented
and ambitious.
He shouldn't be stuck in this small agency.
Jiaojiao.
But have you ever thought about
how hard it is for him to let go?
He has great talent,
but he gave up the top of the Star Cloud.
He has lofty aspirations,
but he is willing to stay here.
What is he doing for?
Jiaojiao.
Before this,
I stood firmly on your side.
But today I want to say something for him.
He deserves it.
Father.
Why do you mention him again?
If he becomes Yue's subordinate,
it won't be good for us.
What do you mean by reading the room?
Look at the people you've found.
The official has already shown displeasure.
Are you going to make it worse?
I...
Father,
here's the new green tea you asked for.
By the way,
where is Cheng Qi now?
I don't know.
How could you not know?
Didn't you go to see him before?
I did try to persuade him to write for the Emperor,
but he refused.
See, I told you.
If he gets to the Emperor,
he'll spill everything
he's done.
We'd better
get rid of him now.
Use your head!
The Emperor wants him back,
and now he's in trouble.
The Emperor will investigate.
If we don't kill him,
then we might as well
ruin him.
Ruin him?
Cheng Qi hasn't met the Emperor yet.
As long as we ruin his reputation,
the Emperor
will definitely not appoint him.
It's a good idea.
We can give it a try.
Are you sure?
That depends on your precious daughter
if she's still protecting her lover.
I know what I'm doing.
Don't let me down.
I understand.
Go.
If this doesn't work,
it can still stall for a few days,
until Langyue's money comes back.
If it works,
the Emperor won't hold
your recommendation of Ling Feng against you.
[We can]
[get out of the trouble.]
Why can't I print?
I want to print 3,000 copies this time.
I've brought the money.
Others' books are okay,
but why can't I print
Cheng Qi's book?
Why?
If you don't give me a reason today,
I'll report you for market bullying.
Cheng Qi's work for the Starry Sky Meeting
is a copy.
A copy?
You should know it best,
Mr. Su.
What are you talking about?
Do you have any evidence?
Please behave yourself.
The news
has spread throughout the book industry.
No one in the capital or the country
is willing to print his books.
I don't believe it.
Hey.
Mr. Sun.
Post this.
We'll buy back
Cheng Qi's books at 70% off.
Got it.
Go.
We want a refund!
Refund the books!
The Cloud Bureau said
Cheng Qi plagiarized,
so they're not selling his books anymore
and will refund
or offer 70% off.
We want refunds for these too!
Yes, refund the books!
Refund the books!
That's the Cloud Bureau's policy.
have nothing to do with me.
I, Meng Feifei, do not accept returns
on anything I sell.
No returns!
And,
with a receipt from me,
you get 20% off all future purchases.
-Who wants that? -What's that?
Who cares?
I'll never come back here.
Yes, let's go.
They won't come even if they beg me.
These people are really fickle.
They begged you to buy when they liked it,
now they disdain it like this.
It's fine.
They are
saving me money.
It's been rumored recently that
Cheng Qixing's works at the Starry Sky Assembly
are all plagiarized.
Moreover,
they say
he and that female escort
are actually fake married,
just to gain sympathy
and help him get on the Starry Cloud List.
Do you have evidence?
Both witnesses and evidence are present.
This is absurd!
Your Majesty, please calm your anger.
I failed in my duties.
Please punish me.
This is not your fault.
Rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Then
how should we deal with Cheng Qi?
He's just a storyteller.
He's neither a traitor
nor an official.
How should we deal with him?
Forget it.
As for Langyue,
the Princess suddenly announced her marriage.
The matter of the speech contest
will be discussed later.
Yes.
I called you here today
because I have something to announce.
Ten days later,
the day I promised to escort Princess Langyue
is coming.
But all the bookshops in the capital
refuse to print Cheng Qi's books.
From today,
all the members and their families
should transcribe the book as much as possible
to complete as many orders as possible.
Can our handwriting
be readable?
As long as it can be understood.
Gong Xifacaizi.
Don't you like writing
all sorts of things?
You two write more.
Got it, My Lord.
Tang Xin, Feifei,
you two are good at writing.
You write more.
No problem.
Jian,
you are good at manual work.
You are in charge of binding.
It would be even better
if there's something that can make them
copy faster.
Jiaojiao,
have you forgotten my invention?
This, this...
Take a look.
That's amazing.
Alright, alright.
Come on.
Don't worry.
Are you injured?
Are your men back?
Yes.
I thought they were good fighters.
They're not as good as the escort agency.
What are they delivering?
Why are there silver ingots
from the Yun State and Langyue?
The ingots Yikeba transported to the Yun State
were from Langyue.
And the ingots escorted by the agency were from the Yun State.
Judging by the number of chests,
there are more coming
than going back.
No wonder it's hard to investigate.
Yikeba also has close ties
with those silver-making tribes.
He's helping people from the Yun State exchange money.
Do you know who it is?
The one in charge of escorting is Fu Xiang.
He's the Grand Preceptor's man.
Slow down, My Lord.
How did you get hurt like this?
Father.
As usual,
I took a detour to hand over the escort money.
As soon as I entered the Langyue,
a group of bandits appeared out of nowhere.
Without saying a word,
they started attacking.
I don't know what grudges they hold.
Are they
from Langyue
or the Yun State?
Are they robbing the escort?
It was dark. I didn't see them clearly.
Some of them have weapons from Langyue,
and some are dressed in Yun State's style.
But
they also killed Langyue people.
I don't think they're robbing the escort.
Did you get the receipt of the escort order?
Father,
I'm dying here,
and you're worried about a receipt?
Just tell me if you got it!
So you do know to save your own skin.
For now,
just lay low outside.
Don't let anyone know you're back.
Why?
Just do as you're told.
Hurry up!
Don't hold me.
Everything is packed.
3,000 books in total.
Each one is flat.
My son-in-law,
are you really going to meet the Princess?
Uncle,
what are you talking about?
I was framed.
I have to go in person
to reassure her.
I see.
You just want to be with Jiaojiao.
No need to make up excuses.
Don't buy me so many things.
Just come back safely.
Don't worry.
Nothing will be delayed.
Cheng Qi,
come here.
This Langyue Wine
is tasty and easy to drink.
You know what I mean, right?
Thank you, Grandpa.
Let's go.
Go.
Cheng Qi actually used colloquial language.
The style is crude.
He actually indulges himself like this.
Shameless.
Disgraceful.
Don't be upset, my lady.
It's not worth it
to be mad at him.
Yeah.
I can't even
get his favor.
What am I?
I'm worthless.
Give it to me.
What is this?
Don't you hate Cheng Qi?
Even you want to betray me?
You're a two-faced
hypocrite!
Miss, I wouldn't dare.
This...
This was bought by a friend of mine.
Tell me,
what's so good about this tacky thing?
The scholar is concerned about the Escort Agency.
The young escort.
Grandpa.
Brother.
Gong Xi, Fai Cai. [*Happy New Year]
Uncle.
They love each other.
They trust each other.
Although they would fight for chicken legs,
[and slack off,]
[or bicker and argue,]
[they still]
[follow their hearts.]
[They are lucky to have each other,]
[and I'm lucky to have them.]
Let someone else
do the dirty and hard work.
What are you afraid of?
I was wrong.
You're good for nothing
but causing trouble!
From now on,
you'll stay here and reflect on your mistakes.
Don't you dare go anywhere!
My lady!
Are you alright?
My lady,
I won't leave you.
You treat me like your own sister.
I will never betray you!
You are my family!
Ying,
you even
enjoy reading this novel.
It seems that Cheng Qi
made the right choice.
My lady,
I just wanted to read it to understand
and help you strategize.
but she accidentally
read a bit more.
Then tell me,
what's so good
about this script?
My lady,
I haven't had much formal education,
and I don't understand the words
from the Starry Sky Assembly.
I can't comprehend them.
But Cheng Qi's scripts
have touched my heart.
Then go buy the complete set.
My lady, what do you mean?
I want to read them too.
Go ahead.
Yes,
I'll go right away.
Good.
Nice.
He took a different approach
to kill two birds with one stone.
So
he borrowed this
and went back to the agency.
Yes.
The key is
that the bookshop in Yunjing didn't cooperate with him.
So
all these were transcribed and printed
by the Su's Agency.
They are united.
They are better than us.
It is said that
these books
were customized by Princess Langyue.
Soon,
The Su's Escort Agency will send them to Klare City.
I guess
it's time for someone to wake up.
But it's not the critical moment now.
Please let them relax.
In this way,
they will reveal more clues.
Let's see what they'll do next.
You're wise, Your Majesty.
Please rest assured.
I will send someone to protect them.
Yesterday, I got a message from Langyue.
They said they didn't get the escort fee.
But today, you said
it was delivered.
Then tell me,
who should I believe?
Your Excellency,
the escort agency has completed the handover.
Here's the receipt.
They said they didn't receive it.
That means they didn't receive it.
For all these years,
I've never wronged a courier agency.
Go and deliver the goods, then come back.
But Grand Preceptor,
it was robbed after the handover.
It has nothing to do
with the escort agency.
If the escort was robbed,
that means we didn't get it.
Fix it up quickly,
or I'll take your house.
Get out.